Research and the University Graduate School records, 1962-2003 C323
Indiana University Archives
- University centers – Proposed, 1974-2000
  - Rural Center for the Study and Prevention of HIV/STD, 1994-1999 (Box 11)
  - Russian and East European Institute, 1988-1998 (Box 11)
  - Scientific Computing and Applied Mathematics Institute (Box 11)
    - 1985-1990 (Box 11)
    - 1986-1998 (Box 11)
  - Theatre Computer Visualization Center, 1992 (Box 11)
  - West African Languages Institute, 1991-1999 (Box 11)
- University centers – Proposed – Not approved, 1997-1999 (Box 12)
  - Center for Environmental Stewardship in Higher Education, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Center for Underwater Science, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Center on Public Leadership and Service, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Hamilton/Lugar Center, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Indiana University International Resource Center, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Leadership Research Institute, 1998 (Box 12)
- RUGS centers, 1962-2002
  - Advanced Research and Technology Institute (ARTI) – President Search (Box 12)
    FILES RESTRICTED
    - Advertising, 2001 (Box 12)
    - Candidates (Box 12)
      - Bailey, T. Dan, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
      - Florance, Sam V., Jr., 2001-2002 (Box 12)
      - Hurrell, John G.R., 2001-2002 (Box 12)
      - Long, Mark S., 2001-2002 (Box 12)
      - Vennare, Raymond F., 2001-2002 (Box 12)
    - Committee Files, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Committee List and ARTI Board, 2001 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
    - Interviews, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
    - Job Description and Organizational Chart, 1998-2001 (Box 12)
  - American Indian Studies, 1984-1999 (Box 12)
  - Anthropological Center for Training and Research in Global Environmental Change (ACT) (Box 12)
    - 1989-1993 (Box 12)
    - 1994-1999 (Box 12)
  - Art Museum (Box 12)
    - 1993-1997 (Box 12)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 12)
  - Arts Administration (Box 12)
    - 1980-1990 (Box 12)
    - Budget (Box 12)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 12)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 12)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 12)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 12)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 12)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 12)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1998-2001 (Box 12)
  - Asian Studies Research Institute (Box 12)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 12)
  - Bureau for Educational Studies and Testing (BEST) (Box 12)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 12)
  - Center for Excellence in Education (CEE) (Box 12)
    - 1983-1986 (Box 12)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 12)
    - 1988-1991 (Box 12)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 12)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 12)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 12)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 12)
    - Annual Reports, 1993-2000 (Box 13)
    - AT&T, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Budget (Box 13)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 13)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 13)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 13)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 13)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 13)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 13)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 13)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 13)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 13)
    - Policy Committee, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Research & Development, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Review Binder, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Wisdom Tools, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - Center for History Making in America (CHMA) (Box 13)
    - 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - 1991-1998 (Box 13)
    - Budget (Box 14)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 14)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 14)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 14)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 14)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 14)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - Center for Math Education, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - Center for Research into Anthropological Foundations of Technology (CRAFT), 1989-1999 (Box 14)
  - Center for the Study of History and Memory, 1989-1999 (Box 14)
    - 1971-1979 (Box 14)
    - 1980 (Box 14)
    - 1981 (Box 14)
    - 1982-1999 (Box 14)
  - Center for the Study of Institutions, Population & Environmental Change (CIPEC), 1996-1999 (Box 14)
  - Center for Survey Research (Box 14)
    - 1985-1999 (Box 14)
    - Advisory Committee, 1982-1993 (Box 14)
  - Center on Congress, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - Computer Technology Assisting Center (CTAC) – Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - Cyclotron Facility (IUCF) (Box 14)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 14)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - 1986-1989 (Box 14)
    - 1990 (Box 14)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 14)
    - 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - 1994, (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 14)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 14)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 15)
    - Annual Reports, 1994-1998 (Box 15)
    - Cooler, 1980-1988 (Box 15)
    - Director Search & Screen (Box 15)
      - 1984-1987 (Box 15)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 15)
    - John Cameron – Review, 1991 (Box 15)
    - Midwest Proton Radiation Institute (MPRI) (Box 15)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 15)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 15)
      - 1997 (Box 15)
      - 1998, (2 folders) (Box 15)
      - 1999, (2 folders) (Box 15)
      - Consultant, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Director Search (Box 15)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 15)
        - Announcement, 1997 (Box 15)
        - Committee Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 15)
        - Committee List, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Proton Therapy Task Force, 1997-1999 (Box 15)
    - Nuclear Theory Center (NTC) Visiting Committee, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Nuclear Science Advisory Committee Meeting, 1981 (Box 15)
    - Review Committee, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Visiting Committee (Box 15)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 15)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 15)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 15)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 15)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 15)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 15)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 15)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 15)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 15)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 15)
      - 1994 (Box 15)
      - 1994-1997 (Box 16)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 16)
      - 1997 (Box 16)
  - East Asian Studies Center (Box 16)
    - 1984-1994 (Box 16)
    - 1993-1998 (Box 16)
    - Annual Reports, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
    - Center for Research on Japanese, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Fine Arts Museum (Box 16)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 16)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 16)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 16)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 16)
  - Forum on Education, 1995-1999 (Box 16)
  - Glenn Black Lab of Archaeology (Box 16)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 16)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 16)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 16)
    - 1977-1999 (Box 16)
    - Advisory Panel, 1976-1998 (Box 16)
    - Annual Reports (Box 16)
      - 1966-1983 (Box 16)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 16)
      - 1988-1991 (Box 16)
      - 1994-1998 (Box 16)
    - Patoka Lake Project, 1977-1978 (Box 16)
    - Search and Screen, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Geological Survey (Box 16)
    - 1991, (4 folders) (Box 16)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 16)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 16)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 16)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 17)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 17)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 17)
    - Director Search, 1985-1999 (Box 17)
    - Operational Plan, 1991 (Box 17)
  - History of Medicine, 1989-1998 (Box 17)
  - Indiana Institute on Disability and Community, 1998-1999 (Box 17)
  - Indiana Molecular Biology Institute (Box 17)
    - 1981-1986 (Box 17)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 17)
    - 1986-1990 (Box 17)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 17)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 17)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 17)
    - 1995-1999 (Box 17)
    - Annual Reports, 1989-1995 (Box 17)
    - Governing Board, 1983-1986 (Box 17)
  - Institute for Advanced Study (Box 17)
    - 1981-1992 (Box 17)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 17)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 17)
    - 1994 (Box 17)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 17)
    - 1995 (Box 17)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 18)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 18)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 18)
    - Annual Reports, 1991-1999 (Box 18)
    - Search and Screen (Box 18)
      - 1982-1987 (Box 18)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 18)
      - 1993-1998 (Box 18)
  - Institute for Drug Abuse Prevention, 1990-1996 (Box 18)
  - Institute for Neural Systems and Plasticity, 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Institute for the Study of Developmental Disabilities (ISDD, formerly Developmental Training Center) (Box 18)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 18)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 18)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 18)
    - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 18)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 18)
    - 1986-1989 (Box 18)
    - 1990-1996 (Box 18)
    - 1996-1998 (Box 18)
    - Advisory Board (Box 18)
      - 1976-1983 (Box 18)
      - 1983-1988 (Box 18)
      - 1983-1988 (Box 18)
    - Advisory and Steering Committees, 1968-1974 (Box 18)
    - Annual Reports (Box 18)
      - 1980-1984 (Box 19)
      - 1985-1988 (Box 19)
      - 1988-1992 (Box 19)
      - 1992-1999 (Box 19)
      - 1999 (Box 19)
    - Grant Application, 1962-1965 (Box 19)
    - Indiana Comprehensive System of Personnel Development, circa 1982 (Box 19)
    - Indiana Resource Center for Autism (IRCA), 1993 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Brochures and Reports (Box 19)
      - circa 1970-1972 (Box 19)
      - circa 1971-1974 (Box 19)
      - circa 1972-1974 (Box 19)
    - Planning, 1964-1969; (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Schroeder, Henry J. – Personnel File, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
    - Sprague, Robert – Personnel File, 1968-1971 (Box 19)
    - Search and Screen, 1995-1996 (Box 19)
    - Wisland, Milton – Personnel File, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Institute for the Study of Human Capabilities (ISHC) (Box 19)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 19)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 19)
    - 1991-1999 (Box 19)
    - Budget (Box 19)
      - 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 19)
      - 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 19)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 19)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 19)
  - Kinsey Institute (Institute for Sex Research) (Box 20)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 20)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 20)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 20)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 20)
    - 1993 (Box 20)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 20)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 20)
    - A.D. Klassen (Box 20)
      - Budget, 1971 (Box 20)
      - General Correspondence (Box 20)
        - 1971 (Box 20)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 20)
    - Annual Reports, 1993-1997 (Box 20)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 20)
      - 1989-1992 (Box 20)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 20)
      - 1991-1993, (2 folders) (Box 20)
      - 1993 (Box 20)
      - 1994 (Box 20)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 20)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 20)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 20)
    - Brochures, 1970-1974 (Box 20)
    - Director Search and Screen, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
    - Reinisch Search and Screen/Retirement, 1982-1993 (Box 20)
  - Laboratory Animal Resources (Box 20)
    - 1966-1976, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1967-1972 (Box 20)
    - 1969-1984 (Box 21)
    - 1972-1981 (Box 21)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 21)
    - 1983-1992 (Box 21)
    - 1993-1999 (Box 21)
    - Animal Lab Care Policies, 1970-1975 (Box 21)
    - Brochures/Guidelines, circa 1967-1968 (Box 21)
    - IUPUI Committee, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Regional Campuses Committees, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Review, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
    - Riggins – Job Classification/Search and Screen, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Search and Screen, 1992-1994 (Box 21)
    - University Committee, 1968-1971 (Box 21)
  - Mathers Museum (Box 21)
    - 1963-1983 (Box 21)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 21)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 21)
    - 1983-1987 (Box 21)
    - 1988-1992 (Box 21)
    - 1992-1997 (Box 21)
    - Annual Reports, 1976-1984 (Box 21)
    - Annual Reports (Box 21)
      - 1976-1984 (Box 21)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 21)
      - 1989 (Box 21)
      - 1991-1999 (Box 21)
    - Advisory/Policy Committee, 1975-1989 (Box 21)
    - Policy Committee, 1992-1997 (Box 21)
    - Search and Screen, 1992-1997 (Box 21)
  - Nuclear Theory Center, 1978-1998 (Box 21)
  - Population Institute for Research and Training (PIRT), 1985-1998 (Box 21)
  - Poynter Center (Box 21)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 22)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 22)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 22)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 22)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 22)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 22)
    - 1979-1984 (Box 22)
    - 1985-1990 (Box 22)
    - 1990-1994 (Box 22)
    - 1994-1999 (Box 22)
    - Advisory Committee, 1974-1989 (Box 22)
    - Annual Reports, 1981-1999 (Box 22)
  - Research Center for Language and Semiotic Studies (RCLSS), 1971-1972 (Box 22)
  - Research Center for Language and Semiotic Studies (RCLSS) (Box 22)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 22)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 22)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 22)
    - 1974-1975, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Brochures/Publications, circa 1972-1976 (Box 22)
    - Budget (Box 22)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 22)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 23)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 23)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 23)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 23)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 23)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 23)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 23)
    - Development Grant in Semiotics, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
    - Final Report for Semiotics Project, 1976 (Box 23)
    - Internal Review, 1985 (Box 23)
    - MacConnell, Dean, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 23)
      - 1976-1981 (Box 23)
      - 1981-1992 (Box 23)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 23)
      - 1986-1988 (Box 23)
      - 1989-1993 (Box 23)
      - 1990-1992 (Box 23)
      - 1993-2002 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1988-1992 (Box 23)
    - Semiotic Society of America – Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 23)
    - Umiker-Sebeok, Jean – Research Rank, 1986-1989 (Box 23)
    - Visiting Committee (Box 23)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 23)
      - 1978 (Box 23)
      - 1979 (Box 23)
      - 1980 (Box 23)
      - 1981 (Box 23)
      - 1982 (Box 23)
      - 1983 (Box 23)
      - 1984 (Box 23)
      - 1985 (Box 23)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 23)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 23)
      - 1988 (Box 23)
      - 1989 (Box 23)
      - 1990 (Box 23)
      - 1992 (Box 23)
    - Research Center for Library and Information Science, 1972-1976 (Box 23)
  - Research Institute for Inner Asian Studies – Ismatullaev, Khairulla, 1999 (Box 24)
  - Workshop in Political Theory and Policy Analysis (Box 24)
    - 1973-1976 (Box 24)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 24)
    - 1976-1979 (Box 24)
    - 1980-1985 (Box 24)
    - 1986-1990 (Box 24)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 24)
    - 1993-1999 (Box 24)
    - Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Annual Report (Box 24)
      - 1976-1984 (Box 24)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 24)
      - 1989-2002 (Box 24)
      - 1992-1998 (Box 24)
    - Publications, Papers, Brochures, etc. (Box 24)
      - 1973-1975 (Box 24)
      - 1973-1976 (Box 24)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 24)
  - Wrubel Computing Center (WCC) (Box 24)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 24)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 24)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 24)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 24)
    - Reports (Box 24)
      - #105-225, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
      - #226-327, 1973-1976 (Box 24)
    - Reports of Senior Staff Meetings, 1972-1976 (Box 24)
- Restricted Files (Box 25)
  Contains all restricted files of the collection, except "Mathers Museum Search and Screen, 1981-1988," which is housed in Box 26.
- Restricted Files (Box 26)
  Mathers Search files.